{
"quiz1": [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "questionType": "true_false",
    "questionText": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory",
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "options" : ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionType": "true_false",
    "questionText": "Java is an Object Oriented programming language",
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "options" : ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionType": "text_input",
    "questionText": "What the programming languages used for cpp files? (make sure to Capitalize)",
    "correctAnswer": "C Plus Plus",
    "explanation": "cpp is an acronym for C Plus PLus"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionType": "multiple_choice",
    "questionText": "Which of these is the HTML tag for making text bold?",
    "correctAnswer": "<b>",
    "options": ["<p>", "<bold>", "<b>", "<div>"],
    "explanation": "<bold> is not an html tag, and the other tags have different purposes, so it must be <b>"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionType": "text_input",
    "questionText": "What does CPU stand for? (make sure the capitalize)",
    "correctAnswer": "Central Processing Unit",
    "explanation": "CPU is an acronym for Central Processing Unit as it processes most data in the computer"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionType": "multiple_choice",
    "questionText": "What Operating System is developed and maintained by Microsoft?",
    "correctAnswer": "Windows",
    "options": ["Windows", "MacOS", "Linux", "Android"],
    "explanation": "Windows is owned by microsoft, while the others are owned by Apple, Linus Torvalds, and Google respectively"
  },
  {
"id": 6,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "Which is not a Java data type?",
"correctAnswer": "decimal",
"options": ["String", "int", "double", "decimal"],
"explanation": "Floats and doubles store decimal values, but decimal itself is not a data type; String and int are also both valid data types."
},
{
"id": 7,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "_______________ is credited with being the very first computer programmer. (Full name, please)",
"correctAnswer": "Ada Lovelace",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "Mathematician & writer Ada Lovelace(1815-1852) wrote the world's first algorithm to the Analytical Machine. The very first computer programmer was a woman!"
},
{
"id": 8,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "Which OS is developed & used by Apple Inc.?",
"correctAnswer": "iOS",
"options": ["Unix", "iOS", "Windows", "Ubuntu"],
"explanation": "macOS is Apple's operating system for personal computers & workstations; iOS is a system for mobile devices."
},
{
"id": 9,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "Which of the following are object-oriented languages?",
"correctAnswer": ["Python","C++", "Ruby"],
"options": ["Python", "C", "C++", "Ruby"],
"explanation": "C is an imperative procedural language; it does not use classes, inheritance, polymorphism, or other features of OOP."
},
{
"id": 10,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "GIF stands for ________ Interchange Format. (Please capitalize)",
"correctAnswer": "Graphics",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "GIF stands for Graphics Interchange Format."
},
{
"id": 11,
"questionType": "multi_text_input",
"questionTextBefore":"GUI stands for ",
"questionTextBetween":" User ",
"questionTextAfter":".",
"correctAnswer": ["Graphical", "Interface"],
"answerFieldId1":"answer_to_first_blank",
"answerFieldId2":"answer_to_second_blank",
"explanation": "GUI stands for Graphical User Interface."
},
{
"id": 12,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "A binary system uses powers of _____.",
"correctAnswer": "2",
"options": ["4", "2", "16", "8"],
"explanation": "As indicated by the prefix bi-, binary systems use powers of 2."
},
{
"id": 13,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": " Which of the following are functions of an operating system?",
"correctAnswer": ["I/O management","Job scheduling",
"Memory management"],
"options": ["I/O management", "Database management", "Job scheduling", "Memory management"],
"explanation": "Database management is the responsibility of a DBMS, not an operating system. Operating systems do handle I/O management, job scheduling & memory management."
},
{
"id": 14,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "Which of the following is the ascending order of data hierarchy?",
"correctAnswer": "Bit-Byte-Field-Record-File-Database",
"options": ["Bit-Byte-Field-Record-File-Database", "Field-Byte-Bit-Record-Database-File", "Bit-Byte-Record-Field-File-Database", "Byte-Bit-Record-Field-File-Database"],
"explanation": "Bits make up bytes, which make fields, which compose records, which together create files, which ultimately form databases."
},
{
"id": 15,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "SQL stands for Standard _______ Language.",
"correctAnswer": "Query",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "SQL stands for Standard Query Language"
},
{
"id": 16,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "A virus is a computer __________.",
"correctAnswer": "Program",
"options": ["File", "Network", "Program", "Database"],
"explanation": "A virus is a typically destructive PROGRAM that replicates itself by modifying other computer programs & inserting its own code."
},
{
"id": 17,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "Which of the following operations are performed on RAM?",
"correctAnswer": ["Read and write"],
"options": ["Read", "Write & edit", "Read and write", "It depends on the user"],
"explanation": "Both read & write operations can be performed on RAM."
},
{
"id": 18,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "Python requires the use of ;'s at the end of lines of code.",
"correctAnswer": "False",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "Unlike a language like Java, Python DOES NOT require the use of ;'s to end lines of code."
},
{
"id": 19,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "Hash maps/hash tables store key- value pairs.",
"correctAnswer": "True",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "Data IS inserted into hash maps using key-value pairs."
}
  ]
}
